let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does a yellow reflector (cat's eye) placed on the road mean?",
    answer: "No Passing",
    options: [
      "Fire Hydrant",
      "No Passing",
      "Yellow Marks the left side of the road",
      "Safe Passing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When coming to a pedestrian crossing with a raised traffic island in the middle, what must you do?",
    answer: "Only stop and give way if a pedestrian is on your half of the crossing.",
    options: [
      "Only stop and give way if a pedestrian is on your half of the crossing.",
      "Stop and give way if a pedestrian is on any part of the crossing.",
      "Don't Know",
      "Either option is fine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If you are driving a car, what should you do when following another vehicle in wet conditions?",
    answer: "Observe the four-second rule",
    options: [
      "Observe the two-second rule",
      "Observe the four-second rule",
      "Observe the six-second rule",
      "Try to overtake"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When are you allowed to drive across a cycle lane?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "To turn into a driveway",
      "To turn into a side road",
      "To park",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When are you likely to see a slow vehicle bay?",
    answer: "On a hill",
    options: [
      "Approaching a roundabout",
      "On a motorway",
      "On a hill",
      "In the central city"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the maximum speed you may drive if you have a space saver wheel fitted?",
    answer: "80km/h",
    options: [
      "70km/h",
      "80km/h",
      "90km/h",
      "100km/h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When you are turning to the right:",
    answer: "Give three seconds' warning",
    options: [
      "Give three seconds' warning",
      "Give two seconds' warning",
      "Only signal if there are other cars behind or ahead of you",
      "You Don't need to signal"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "For the purpose of applying the Give Way rule, how should an entrance way into a public car park be treated?",
    answer: "As an intersection",
    options: [
      "As an intersection",
      "The vehicle that is there first has right of way",
      "As a one-way street",
      "As a pedestrian crossing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Before making a lane change to your left, you must signal for at least three seconds. What else must you do?",
    answer: "Check your blind spots",
    options: [
      "Check your blind spots",
      "Slow down",
      "Speed up",
      "Use your brake lights to warn other drivers"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Who can put a blue accident sign up?",
      answer: "A police officer",
      options: [
        "An ambulance officer",
        "A police officer",
        "A council officer",
        "A member of the public"
     ]
    },


];
